DAVID BARAHONA HERNÁNDEZ

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address: C/ Bueso Pineda, 39 – G, Madrid, 28043, Spain

➤ Date of Birth: October 5th, 1986 Nationality: Spanish

PROFILE

I am an Aeronautical Engineering graduate from the UPM, Madrid, specializing in Airports and Air Navigation. I have over 3 years' professional experience, working for AENA at Malaga Airport and Deloitte as an IT Strategy Consultant. My main strengths and skills include: Quality Control Knowhow, Project Management and Team Project Expertise and additionally I hold the ITIL Foundation Certificate.

At present, I am improving and furthering my knowledge in the Aviation Industry by studying an Msc in Air Transport Management with ITAérea and I just finished a 5-month Master in Professional English with Vaughan Systems. I am open to opportunities and keen to further develop my experience and skills in a challenging role with a well-regarded company in the Aviation Industry.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

DELOITTE, IT Strategy (January 2011 – October 2013)
SEPI Group - DELOITTE, IT Strategy (September 2010 – December 2010)



Within my Strategic Consulting remit, I mainly worked on projects for the following clients:

- > Santander Bank, S.A. (19 months)
- COBRA GESTIÓN DE INFRAESTRUCTURAS, S.A. (GRUPO COBRA), ACS Servicios Industriales (8 months)
- > Telefónica S.A. (5 months)



My main responsibilities included:

> Functions:

- Participated in a PMO for technology projects in Santander Bank.
- o Defined requirements and developed a staff control tool in a bank.
- Designed an application to incorporate the internal management model of the Organization Department of Santander Bank.

- Led the implementation of a tool for IT service management.
- o Controlled of the evolution of a revenue assurance project.

> Achievements:

- o Perfected a control staff tool by including new countries and features.
- o Created an application with an internal management model.
- Implemented incidents and changes requests in a tool based on ITIL best practices.

AENA, Airport Services Division from Malaga airport. (July 2010 – August 2010)

- > Functions:
 - Perfected the organization and improved quality control of the airport baggage trolley system.
- Achievements:
 - Introduced a new way to measure quality of the airport baggage trolley system.

EDUCATION

Air Transport Management Msc, ITAérea (November 2013 – Now) ITIL Foundation Certificate, APMG-International (December 2012)

Degree in Aeronautical Engineering, UPM, Madrid (September 2004 – June 2010)

Specialization: Airports and Air Navigation

Final Project: "Business Plan from Madrid-Barajas airport" in the UPM, Madrid

FURTHER EDUCATION AND COURSES

- ➤ MIP Professional English Master, Vaughan Sys. (October 2013 March 2014)
- EasyVista Certificate (IT Service Management tool), EV/Deloitte (January 2013)
- Course: Financial principles, Deloitte. (January 2011)

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native language

> English: Professional proficiency

IT SKILLS AND SOFTWARE TOOLS

- Expert user of MS Office (MS Excel, MS Access, MS Word and MS PowerPoint)
- Advanced knowledge of programming in Visual Basic, SQL and EasyVista.

OTHER PERSONAL DATA

- Driving license and own car
- ➤ Willing to travel / relocate

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST